NAYLA AZ ZAHRA

Medan, 20245 | 081271127846 | naylatanjung79@gmail.com

SUMMARY

My name is Nayla Az Zahra, an undergraduate Information Technology student at Universitas Sumatera Utara. I have experience as a public relation staff at DW Talk, as a business development staff at Belajar Ind, and as a secretary at Dharmawangsa English Club.

EXPERIENCE

Public Relation Staff

Jun 2021 – Jul 2023

DW Talk

- Manage negotiations with media partners to determine terms of cooperation
- Develop and disseminate press releases, official statements, and other materials to media partners
- Conduct active monitoring of public response and perception of the organization

Business Development Staff

Aug 2021 - Aug 2022

Belajar Ind

- Increased public awareness of the organization's existence by 30%
- Initiate tutoring programs and workshops as a new source of income for the organization
- · Maximize the organization's funding

Secretary Jan 2021 – Feb 2022

Dharmawangsa English Club

- Organize and schedule meetings and events
- Recording organizational activities
- Filing minutes and reports of organizational agendas

EDUCATION

Information Technology 2023 - Present

Universitas Sumatera Utara

Mathematics and Natural Science

2020 - 2023

SMAS Dharmawangsa Medan

- Top 3 overall outstanding student for three years
- Ranked 1st overall in the second semester

CERTIFICATION

Introduction to Internet of Things

Dec 2023

Cisco Networking Academy

Computer Hardware Basics

Cisco Networking Academy

TOEFL Apr 2023

Score: 547

ACHIEVEMENT

2nd Runner Up

Digital Poster Design

Dharmawangsa Carnaval 2023

The Champion

English SpeechUMSUFEST 2021

2nd Runner Up

Digital Poster Design

Dharmawangsa Carnaval 2022

The Champion

English Essay Writing VEC Anniversary 2020

The Champion

Digital Poster Design

GenRe Movement UMSU 2022

Nov 2023